Guide to the Collection on Prominent Figures in Historical Recorded Sound
Yale University Music Library
- Names, Series I
  - Kaschmann, Giuseppe, 1909–1916 (Folder 517)
  - Kawecka (Folder 518)
  - Kellogg, Clara Louise, 1926 (Folder 519)
  - Kern, Adele, 1929 Jan 5 (Folder 520)
  - Ketten, Henry, 1880 Oct 28 (Folder 521)
  - Ketterer, Eugene (Folder 522)
  - Kiepura, Jan (Folder 523)
  - Kingston, Morgan (Folder 524)
  - Kipnis, Alexander (Folder 525)
  - Kittel, Hermina, 1916 (Folder 526)
  - Kittel, Paul (Folder 527)
  - Kiurina, Berta, 1916, 1930 (Folder 528)
  - Kliebert, Karl (Folder 529)
  - Klose, Margarete, 1937 (Folder 530)
  - Knote, Heinrich, 1914, 1936 (Folder 531)
  - Knupfer, Paul, 1901 (Folder 532)
  - Kolling, Cicil, 1874 (Folder 533)
  - Koenen, Tilly (Folder 534)
  - Konetzni, Hilde (Folder 535)
  - Kontskii, Chevalier de (Folder 536)
  - Korsoff, Lucette, 1906 (Folder 537)
  - Koshetz, Nina, 1930 (Folder 538)
  - Krakamp (Folder 539)
  - Kraus, Ernst (Folder 540)
  - Kraus, Felix von (Folder 541)
  - Krauss, Gabrielle, 1892–1898 (Folder 542)
  - Krauss, Siegmund (Folder 543)
  - Krusceniski, Salomea (Folder 544)
  - Kubelik, Jan, 1904–1908 (Folder 545)
  - Kullmann, Charles (Folder 546)
  - Kurenko, Maria, 1953 (Folder 547)
  - Kurz, Selma (Folder 548)
  - Labia, Maria (Folder 549)
  - Lablache, Luigi (Folder 550)
  - Lahnemann, Otto (Folder 551)
  - Laffitte, Jeanne, 1906 (Folder 552)
  - Laffitte, Léon, 1906 (Folder 553)
  - Landowska, Wanda, 1957 (Folder 554)
  - Lang, Carl (Folder 555)
  - Lanza, Francesco (Folder 556)
  - Lassalle, Jean-Louis, 1894 (Folder 557)
  - Lauri-Volpi, Giacomo (Folder 558)
  - Lawrence, Marjorie (Folder 559)
  - Layolle, 1909 Jan 16 (Folder 560)
  - Lazaro, Hipolito, 1967 (Folder 561)
  - Leblanc, Georgette, 1905, 1960-1965 (Folder 562)
  - Ledbetter, Huddie, 1943 (Folder 563)
  - Lefebure, Yvonne (Folder 564)
  - Lehar, Franz (Folder 565)
  - Lehmann, Lilli, 1898–1899 (Folder 566)
    Photographs.
  - Lehmann, Lilli, 1898–1899 (Folder 567)
    Correspondence, including letters to Victor Maurel.
  - Lehmann, Marie (Folder 568)
  - Leicester Schools Summer Orchestra (Folder 569)
  - Leider, Frieda, 1928 (Folder 570)
  - Leisinger, Elisabeth, 1891 (Folder 571)
  - Leliva, Enzo (Folder 572)
  - Lenza, Enrico de, 1867 (Folder 573)
  - Leon, Maurice (Box 7, Folder 1102)
  - Leonard, Myrtle, 1934 Dec 26 (Folder 574)
  - Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1892 (Folder 575)
  - Leuer, Hubert (Folder 576)
  - Levi, Hermann (Folder 577)
  - Lewis, Bertha (Folder 578)
  - Lewis, Ted (Box 7, Folder 1103)
  - Lind, Jenny (Folder 579)
  - Lind, Jenny (Box 7, Folder 1104)
  - Lindgren, Lydia, 1915–1916 (Folder 580)
  - Lisey, Cesare (Folder 581)
  - List, Eugene (Folder 582)
  - Litta, Giulio, 1891 (Folder 583)
  - Litvinne, Felia, 1900–1919 (Folder 584)
  - Loltgen, Adolf (Folder 585)
  - London, George, 1953 Jan 29 (Folder 586)
  - Longobardi, Luigi (Folder 587)
  - Lordmann, Peter (Folder 588)
  - Lorenz, Julius (Folder 589)
  - Lubert (Folder 590)
  - Lucca, Pauline (Folder 591)
  - Lucchetta, Rita (Folder 592)
  - Lucia, Fernando de, 1898 Dec 15 (Folder 593)
  - Lunn, Louise Kirkby (Folder 594)
  - Lykseth-Skogman, Magna (Folder 595)
  - Lysberg, Charl (Folder 596)
  - Lytton, Henry (Folder 597)
  - Mackenzie, Alexander (Box 7, Folder 1105)
  - Madeira, Jean (Folder 598)
  - Magnard, Albéric (Folder 599)
  - Maikl, Georg, 1916 (Folder 600)
  - Maison, Rene, 1908 (Folder 601)
  - Malibran, Maria Felicità (Folder 602)
  - Malkin, Beata (Folder 603)
  - Malten, Therese (Folder 604)
  - Mamo, Adelaide Borghi (Folder 605)
  - Mancinelli, Luigi, 1895–1898 (Folder 606)
  - Mancinelli, Maniro (Folder 607)
  - Mann, Josef, 1914 (Folder 608)
  - Manna, Rugero (Folder 609)
  - Mantelli, Eugenia (Folder 610)
  - Mapleson, Lionel (Folder 611)
  - Marcel, Lucille, 1910 (Folder 612)
  - Marchal, Gulienne, 1946 (Folder 613)
  - Marchesi, Blanche, 1905 (Folder 614)
  - Marchetti, Filippo (Folder 615)
  - Marchisio, Barbara (Folder 616)
  - Marchisio, Carlotta (Folder 617)
  - Marconi, Francesco, 1903 (Folder 618)
  - Marcy, Jane (Folder 619)
  - Mardones, Jose, 1918 Feb 17 (Folder 620)
  - Mariani, Angelo, 1861 (Folder 621)
  - Marie de l'Isle, Jeanne (Folder 622)
  - Marini, Ignazio (Folder 623)
  - Marinuzzi, Gino (Folder 624)
  - Mario [Giovanni], 1884 (Folder 625)
  - Mario, Queena (Folder 626)
  - Mariotti (Folder 627)
  - Marlowe, Julia (Box 7, Folder 1107)
  - Marsh, Lucy Isabelle (Folder 628)
  - Marteau, Henri (Folder 629)
  - Martin, Riccardo, 1913 (Folder 630)
  - Martinelli, Giovanni, 1919, 1942-1948 (Folder 631)
  - Martinez-Patti, Gino (Folder 632)
  - Marini, Nino, 1975 (Folder 633)
  - Martini, Padre (Folder 634)
  - Martucci, Giuseppe (Folder 635)
  - Mascagni, Pietro, 1895, 1920 (Folder 636)
  - Maskheroni, Enzo (Folder 637)
  - Masi, Mariani, 1888–1896 (Folder 638)
  - Masini, Angelo, 1901 Feb 10 (Folder 639)
  - Mason, Edith (Folder 640)
  - Mason, Laura (Folder 641)
  - Massenet, Jules, 1875–1885 (Folder 642)
  - Materna, Amalia Friedrich (Folder 643)
  - Matray, Desider (Folder 644)
  - Mattei, Tito (Folder 645)
  - Matteo da Brescia (Folder 646)
  - Mattfeld, Marie, 1912 (Folder 647)
  - Matzenauer, Margaret, 1920, 1957 (Folder 648)
  - Maubourg, Jane, circa 1906 (Folder 649)
  - Maurel, Victor (Folder 650)
    Photographs and articles.
  - Maurel, Victor (Folder 651)
    Correspondence and promotional materials, including correspondence to Lilli Lehmann.
  - Mayer, Charles (Folder 652)
  - Mayo, Eleanor (Folder 653)
  - Mayr, Richard, 1929–1932 (Folder 654)
  - Mayr, Simone (Folder 655)
  - Mazzoleni, Ester (Folder 656)
  - McCormack, John, 1939 (Folder 657)
  - McCracken, James (Folder 658)
  - McPherson, Aimee Semple (Box 7, Folder 1106)
  - Meade, Anna (Folder 659)
  - Meader, George (Folder 660)
  - Meader, George and Maria, 1914 Dec 22 (Box 7, Folder 1108)
  - Medtner, Nicolas, 1879 Dec 24 (Folder 661)
  - Mehul, Stefan Nicole (Folder 662)
  - Mei-Figner, Medea (Folder 663)
  - Meisle, Kathryn, 1934 Jan 14 (Folder 664)
  - Meister, Carl, 1914 (Folder 665)
  - Melba, Nellie, 1893–1924 (Folder 666)
  - Melchior, Lauritz, 1936 (Folder 667)
  - Meltzer, Charles H. (Folder 668)
  - Mengelberg, Willem, 1932 (Folder 669)
  - Menuhin, Yehuoi, 1938 (Folder 670)
  - Mercadante, Saveria (Folder 671)
  - Merchetti, Filippo (Folder 672)
  - Merode, Cleo de (Folder 673)
  - Merrill, Robert (Folder 674)
  - Messager, André, 1891 (Folder 675)
  - Meyerbeer, Giacomo (Folder 676)
  - Milanov, Zinka (Folder 677)
  - Miller, William (Folder 678)
  - Millidge, Henry (Folder 679)
  - Mirabell (Folder 680)
  - Miura, Tamaki, 1921 (Folder 681)
  - Molinari, Bernardino (Folder 682)
  - Mongini, Pietro (Folder 683)
  - Monte, Toti dal (Folder 684)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1933 (Folder 685)
  - Montdesanto, Luigi, 1953 (Folder 686)
  - Moore, Grace, 1934 May 31 (Folder 687)
  - Moore, Mary, 1934 Dec 31 (Folder 688)
  - Morati, Andre, 1907 (Folder 689)
  - Morena, Berta, 1912 (Folder 690)
  - Moriani, Napoleone (Folder 691)
  - Morlacchi, Francesco, 1825 (Folder 692)
  - Mortier, Gerard (Folder 693)
  - Moscona, Nicola, 1954 (Folder 694)
  - Moser, Andreas (Folder 695)
  - Moszkowski, Moritz, 1879 (Folder 696)
  - Mottl-Fassbender, Zdenka, 1912 (Folder 697)
  - Mukle, May, 1912 Dec 2 (Folder 698)
  - Muller, Maria, 1932 (Folder 699)
  - Muhlmann, Adolf, 1908 (Folder 700)
  - Muratore, Lucien, 1917–1922 (Folder 701)
  - Muzio, Claudia, 1915, 1929 (Folder 702)
  - Muzio, Emanuele, 1890 (Folder 703)
  - Namara, Marguerite (Folder 704)
  - Napoli, Gennaro (Folder 705)
  - Nast, Minnie (Folder 706)
  - Navel, Franz, 1903 (Folder 707)
  - Navarini, Francesco (Folder 708)
  - Naudin, Emilio (Folder 709)
  - Nelli, Herva, 1949 May 22 (Folder 710)
  - Nemeth, Maria (Folder 711)
  - Nespoulous, Marthe (Folder 712)
  - Nevada, Emma and Mignon, 1938 (Folder 713)
  - Nicholls, Agnes, 1926 (Folder 714)
  - Nicolini, Ernesto (Folder 715)
  - Nielsen, Alice, 1926–1935 (Folder 716)
  - Nikisch, Artur (Folder 717)
  - Nikita, Louise, 1894 (Folder 718)
  - Niles, John Jacob (Box 7, Folder 1109)
  - Nilsson, Christine (Folder 719)
  - Nini, Mariana Barbiere (Folder 720)
  - Noldi, Helen, 1908 (Folder 721)
  - Nordica, Lillian, 1895, 1909 (Folder 722)
  - Nordica, Lillian, 1903 Apr 11 (Box 7, Folder 1110)
  - Ober, Margarete Arndt (Folder 723)
  - Oberländer, Alfred (Folder 724)
  - Olcott, Chauncey (Folder 725)
  - Oldham, Derek (Folder 726)
  - Olitzka, Rosa (Folder 727)
  - Olszewska, Maria, 1930 (Folder 728)
  - O'Mara, Joseph, 1909 (Folder 729)
  - Onegin, Sigrid, 1928 (Folder 730)
  - Orgeni, Aglaja (Folder 731)
  - Ortolani, Angelica (Folder 732)
  - Osten, Eva Plaschke von der (Folder 733)
  - O'Sullivan, Denis (Folder 734)
  - Paalen, Bella, 1910–1946 (Folder 735)
  - Pacary, Lina (Folder 736)
  - Paccini, Giovanni (Folder 737)
  - Paderewski, Ignacy Jan (Folder 738)
  - Paër, Ferdinando (Folder 739)
  - Paër, Ferdinando (Box 7, Folder 1111)
  - Paganini, Nicolo, 1819 (Folder 740)
  - Pagliaro, Rocco, 1896 (Folder 741)
  - Paisiello, Giovanni (Folder 742)
  - Paisiello, Giovanni, 1848 (Box 7, Folder 1112)
  - Palliser, Esther, 1900 Oct 11 (Folder 743)
  - Palloni, Gaetano (Folder 744)
  - Palman, Ilka Kinsky von, 1896–1902 (Folder 745)
  - Paloschi, Giovanni (Folder 746)
  - Palumbo, Costantino (Folder 747)
  - Pandolfini, Angelica (Folder 748)
  - Panetti, Joan, 1974–1976 (Folder 749)
  - Panizza, Ettore, 1934 (Folder 750)
  - Panofka, Enrico, 1866 (Folder 751)
  - Pantaleoni, Romilda (Folder 752)
  - Panzera, Charles (Folder 753)
  - Paoli, Antonio, 1907 (Folder 754)
  - Papato (Folder 755)
  - Papier, Rosa (Folder 756)
  - Pardey, Maly, 1912 (Folder 757)
  - Parsi-Pettinella, Armida (Folder 758)
  - Pasero, Tancredi, 1929 (Folder 759)
  - Pasquali, Bernice de (Folder 760)
  - Patane, Franco, 1962 (Folder 761)
  - Peerce, Jan (Folder 762)
  - Penco, Rosina (Folder 763)
  - Pennarini, Alois (Folder 764)
  - Perea, Emilio (Folder 765)
  - Perez, A. (Folder 766)
  - Perny, Paul Hubert (Folder 767)
  - Perosi, Lorenzo, 1872–1899 (Folder 768)
  - Perotti (Folder 769)
  - Perras, Margarete (Folder 770)
  - Peters, Roberta (Folder 771)
  - Petrella, Errico (Folder 772)
  - Petru, Josie, 1904 Dec 5 (Folder 773)
  - Petter, Franz (Folder 774)
  - Pfitzner, Hans (Folder 775)
  - Philipp, Isadore (Folder 776)
  - Piaf, Edith (Folder 777)
  - Piatti, Alfredo (Folder 778)
  - Piave, Francesco Mona (Folder 779)
  - Piccaver, Alfred (Folder 780)
  - Piccinni, Nicola (Folder 781)
  - Piccolomini, Maria (Folder 782)
  - Pichler, Max (Folder 783)
  - Pickford, Mary (Folder 784)
  - Pierne, Gabriel (Folder 785)
  - Pini-Corsi, Antonio, 1897, 1912 (Folder 786)
  - Pinkert, Regina (Folder 787)
  - Pinza, Ezio (Folder 788)
  - Pirani, Eugenio (Folder 789)
  - Pistori (Folder 790)
  - Pius X, Pope, 1908 Apr 2 (Box 7, Folder 1113)
  - Plaichinger, Thila, 1904 (Folder 791)
  - Plançon, Pol, 1878-1897 (Folder 792)
  - Platania, Pietro (Folder 793)
  - Pogánny, G. (Folder 794)
  - Ponchielli, Amilcare (Folder 795)
  - Pons, Lily (Folder 796)
  - Ponselle, Rosa, 1929, 1958 (Folder 797)
  - Popovici, Demeter, 1894 (Folder 798)
  - Porter, Cole (Folder 799)
  - Prandelli, Giacinto, 1952 (Folder 800)
  - Preuss, Arthur, 1904 (Folder 801)
  - Puccini, Giacomo (Folder 802)
  - Puccini, Giocomo, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 1114)
  - Pugno, Raoul (Folder 803)
  - Pullé, Count Leopold (Folder 804)
  - Rabboni, Giuseppe (Folder 805)
  - Radford, Robert (Folder 806)
  - Raff, Joachim (Folder 807)
  - Rains, Leon (Folder 808)
  - Raisa, Rosa, 1922-1929, 1954 (Folder 809)
  - Ratti, Nina, 1914 (Folder 810)
  - Ravogli, Sofia (Folder 811)
  - Raymond, George (Folder 812)
  - Refice, Licinio, 1899 (Folder 813)
  - Reichmann, Theodor, 1901 (Folder 814)
  - Reimers, Paul (Folder 815)
  - Reisman, Leo (Box 8, Folder 1115)
  - Reiss, Albert, 1908 (Folder 816)
  - Remond, Fritz (Folder 817)
  - Renard, Maurice, 1910 (Folder 818)
  - Rendano, Alfonso (Folder 819)
  - Reszke, Edouard de, 1881, 1895-1897 (Folder 820)
  - Reszke, Jean de, 1895–1901 (Folder 821)
  - Rethberg, Elizabeth (Folder 822)
  - Rheinberger, Josef (Folder 823)
  - Rhys-Parker, Isabel and Michael (Folder 824)
  - Ricci, Luigi, 1859 (Folder 825)
  - Richter, Hans (Folder 826)
  - Ricordi, Emilio (Folder 827)
  - Rimini, Giacomo (Folder 828)
  - Rinaldi, Giovanni (Folder 829)
  - Ritschel, Hans (Folder 830)
  - Rizzi, Giuseppe (Folder 831)
  - Roakel, Joseph (Folder 832)
  - Robertson, Forbes, 1898 Sep 21 (Box 8, Folder 1116)
  - Robin, Mado (Folder 833)
  - Röder, Martino (Folder 834)
  - Rolis, Marta (Folder 835)
  - Roma, Lisa, 1928 (Folder 836)
  - Ronchetti-Monteviti, S. (Folder 837)
  - Ronconi, Giorgio (Folder 838)
  - Rooy, Anton van, 1904–1908 (Folder 839)
  - Rosen, Max, 1920 (Folder 840)
  - Rosenthal, Moriz (Folder 841)
  - Rosenthal, Moriz (Box 8, Folder 1117)
  - Rossi, Lauro (Folder 842)
  - Rossini, Gioacchino, 1800 (Folder 843)
  - Rossini, Gioachino, 1847, 1867 (Box 8, Folder 1118)
  - Roswaenge, Helge, 1932–1937 (Folder 844)
  - Rothier, Leon (Folder 845)
  - Rothmuhl, Nicolaus (Folder 846)
  - Rotoli, Augusto (Folder 847)
  - Roussel, Albert, 1933 (Folder 848)
  - Rubini, Giovanni Battista (Folder 849)
  - Rubini, Giovanni Battista, 1840 (Box 8, Folder 1119)
  - Rüsche-Endorf, Cacilie (Folder 850)
  - Ruffo, Titta, 1922–1952 (Folder 851)
  - Ruffo, Titta, 1908 Feb 28 (Box 8, Folder 1120)
  - Rupenich, Emilio (Folder 852)
  - Russ, Giannina (Folder 853)
  - Russ, Giannina, 1910 Nov 15 (Box 8, Folder 1121)
  - Rysanek, Leonie, 1956 (Folder 854)
  - Sack, Erna (Folder 855)
  - Saint Säens, Camille, 1911 (Folder 856)
  - Sala, Marco (Folder 857)
  - Salden, Ida (Folder 858)
  - Salignac, J. Thomas, 1896–1908 (Folder 859)
  - Saltzmann, Minnie (Folder 860)
  - Salvini, Tomaso (Folder 861)
  - Salvioni, Mierna (Folder 862)
  - Samara, Spiro (Folder 863)
  - Samaroff-Stokowski, Olga, 1929 (Folder 864)
  - Sammarco, G. Mario, 1908–1914 (Folder 865)
  - San Fiorenzo (Folder 866)
  - San Francisco (Folder 867)
  - Sanden Aline (Folder 868)
  - Sanderson, Sybil (Folder 869)
  - Santley, Charles, 1914, 1963 (Folder 870)
  - Sapio, Clementine de Vere, 1911 (Folder 871)
  - Sarasate, Pablo de (Folder 872)
  - Sarria, Enrico (Folder 873)
  - Saville, Frances (Folder 874)
  - Sayou, Bidu, 1942 (Folder 875)
  - Sbolci, Jefte (Folder 876)
  - Sbolis, Jefte, 1874 (Folder 877)
  - Scalchi, Sofia (Folder 878)
  - Scampini, Agusto, 1908 Jan 27 (Box 8, Folder 1122)
  - Scaramberg, Emile, 1900 (Folder 879)
  - Scaria, Emil (Folder 880)
  - Scheff, Fritzi, 1905–1908 (Folder 881)
  - Scheffer, Ary (Folder 882)
  - Scheidemantel, Karl (Folder 883)
  - Scheidt, Selma vom (Folder 884)
  - Schipa, Tito, 1925–1930 (Folder 885)
  - Schipper, Emil, 1915 Dec 29 (Folder 886)
  - Schira, Francesco (Folder 887)
  - Schlusnus, Heinrich, 1931 Jan 7 (Folder 888)
  - Schmedes, Eric, 1901 (Folder 889)
  - Schoen-Rene, Anna Eugenie, 1886, 1929-1933 (Folder 890)
  - Schoen-Rene, Anna Eugenie (Box 8, Folder 1123)
  - Schoffel, Joseph (Folder 891)
  - Schöne, Lotte, 1931 (Folder 892)
  - Scholz, Bernhard, 1874 (Folder 893)
  - Schorr, Friedrich, 1931 (Folder 894)
  - Schramm, Peter, 2000 Oct 24 (Folder 895)
  - Schrodter, Fritz, 1896–1916 (Folder 896)
  - Schubert, Franz (Folder 897)
  - Schumann, Robert (Folder 898)
  - Schürmann, Harry (Folder 899)
  - Schumann, Clara (Folder 900)
  - Schumann, Elizabeth, 1936 (Folder 901)
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine, 1898, 1913-1915 (Folder 902)
  - Schutz (Folder 903)
  - Schwarz, Max, 1879 Jul 30 (Folder 904)
  - Schwarz, Vera, 1929 (Folder 905)
  - Scotti, Antonio, 1913, 1929 (Folder 906)
  - Scotti, Antonio (Box 8, Folder 1124)
  - Scuderi, Salvatore (Folder 907)
  - Sembach, Johannes, 1922 (Folder 908)
  - Sembrich, Marcella, 1904–1909 (Folder 909)
  - Servais, Joseph (Folder 910)
  - Setti, Giulio, 1929 Nov 2 (Folder 911)
  - Sgamboti, Giovanni (Folder 912)
  - Sharlow, Myrna, 1931 (Folder 913)
  - Sharp, Eileen (Folder 914)
  - Sheehan, Joseph F. (Folder 915)
  - Sheffield, Leo (Folder 916)
  - Sibelius, Jean, 1937–1948 (Folder 917)
  - Sibelius, Jean (Box 8, Folder 1125)
  - Sickesz, Jan (Folder 918)
  - Siems, Margarethe (Folder 919)
  - Siepi, Cesare, 1900 (Folder 920)
  - Singer, Teresina (Folder 921)
  - Sinimberghi, Gino, 1954 (Folder 922)
  - Sivori, Camillo, 1891 (Folder 923)
  - Smirnov, Dimitri (Folder 924)
  - Sobinov, Leonnid Vitalevich, 1901-1910, 1951 (Folder 925)
  - Sobrino, Luisa (Folder 926)
  - Soffredini, Alfred (Folder 927)
  - Solera, Temistocle (Folder 928)
  - Solti, Marcellana (Folder 929)
  - Somma, Antonio (Folder 930)
  - Sommer, Kurt (Folder 931)
  - Sousa, John Phillip (Box 8, Folder 1126)
  - Spani, Hina, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 1127)
  - Spemann, Heinrich (Folder 932)
  - Spezia, Maria (Box 8, Folder 1128)
  - Spontini, Gaspare, 1830 (Folder 933)
  - Stagno, Roberto, 1897 (Folder 934)
  - Stanford, Charles V. (Box 8, Folder 1129)
  - Steber, Eleanor (Folder 935)
  - Steber, Eleanor (Box 8, Folder 1130)
  - Stehle, Adelina, 1891 Mar 29 (Folder 936)
  - Stern, Blake, 1972–1988 (Folder 937)
  - Stevens, Rise (Folder 938)
  - Stignani, Ebe (Folder 939)
  - Stolz, Robert (Folder 940)
  - Stolz, Teresa, 1869 (Folder 941)
  - Storchio, Rosina, 1912 (Folder 942)
  - Stracchiari, Riccardo, 1910, 1953 (Folder 943)
  - Strätz, Carl (Folder 944)
  - Straus, Edouard (Folder 945)
  - Strauss, Johann (Folder 946)
  - Strauss, Josef (Folder 947)
  - Strauss, Richard (Folder 948)
  - Strauss, Richard (Box 8, Folder 1131)
  - Strazza, Giovannina (Folder 949)
  - Stritt, Albert (Folder 950)
  - Strong, Susan (Folder 951)
  - Sullivan, Arthur, 1874–1904 (Box 8, Folder 1132)
  - Sulva, Marguerita, 1912, 1929 (Folder 952)
  - Sumac, Yma (Folder 953)
  - Sunelius, Marie, 1956 May 6 (Folder 954)
  - Svanholm, Set, 1950–1951 (Folder 955)
  - Swarthout, Gladys, 1937 May 30 (Folder 956)
  - Swolfs, Laurent, 1907 (Folder 957)
  - Tadolini, Eugenia (Folder 958)
  - Taglioni, Marie (Folder 959)
  - Tajo, Italo (Folder 960)
  - Talexis, Amelia (Folder 961)
  - Tamagno, Francesco, 1894–1902 (Folder 962)
  - Tamagno, Francesco (Box 8, Folder 1133)
  - Tamberlick, Enrico, 1864 (Folder 963)
  - Tänzler, Hans (Folder 964)
  - Tauber, Richard (Folder 965)
  - Taucher, Curt, 1922–1923 (Folder 966)
  - Tausig, Karl (Folder 967)
  - Tebaldi, Renata, 1956 (Folder 968)
  - Telva, Marion, 1929 (Folder 969)
  - Tempest, Marie (Box 8, Folder 1134)
  - Tennyson, Alfred Lord, 1977–1984 (Folder 970)
  - Tennyson, Alfred Lord (Box 8, Folder 1135)
  - Terrani, Irma (Folder 971)
  - Terry, Ellen (Folder 972)
  - Terry, Ellen, 1906 Sep 12 (Box 8, Folder 1136)
  - Teschemacher, Margarette, 1938 (Folder 973)
  - Tessarin, Angelo (Folder 974)
  - Tetrazzini, Luisa, 1902–1921 (Folder 975)
  - Tetrazzini, Luisa (Box 8, Folder 1137)
  - Teyte, Maggie (Folder 976)
  - Thalberg, Sigismond (Folder 977)
  - Thill, Georges, 1921 Mar 26 (Folder 978)
  - Thomas, Ambrose (Folder 979)
  - Thomas, Theodore (Folder 980)
  - Thornton, Edna (Folder 981)
  - Thursby, Eleanor, 1902 (Folder 982)
  - Tiberini, Mario (Folder 983)
  - Tibbett, Lawrence (Folder 984)
  - Tietjens, Theresa (Folder 985)
  - Tijssen, Josef (Folder 986)
  - Todard (Folder 987)
  - Tömlich, Richard (Folder 988)
  - Tokatyan, Armand, 1929 (Folder 989)
  - Torme, Mel (Box 8, Folder 1138)
  - Torresella, Fanny, 1888 (Folder 990)
  - Torricella, Metaura, 1886 (Folder 991)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1909, 1920-1921 (Folder 992)
    Includes manuscript of a musical excerpt and correspondence to Victor Maurel.
  - Tosti, Francesco Paolo, 1914 (Folder 993)
  - Tour, Georges Imbart de la (Folder 994)
  - Tozzi, Giorgio (Folder 995)
  - Traubel, Helen (Folder 996)
  - Tua, Teresina, 1881 (Folder 997)
  - Unidentified Cards (Folder 998)
  - Unidentified Photos, 1883–1894 (Folder 999)
  - Urlus, Jacques (Folder 1000)
  - Vaccae, Salvatore (Box 8, Folder 1139)
  - Vaccai, Niccola (Folder 1001)
  - Valero, Fernando (Folder 1002)
  - Valletti, Cesare, 1953 (Folder 1003)
  - Vallier, Jean (Folder 1004)
  - Van Dyck, Ernest (Folder 1005)
  - Vanni, Marcoux, 1930 (Folder 1006)
  - Vannuccini, Luigi (Folder 1007)
  - Vanzo, Alain (Folder 1008)
  - Varelli,E., 1883 (Folder 1009)
  - Varesi, Felice, 1983 Mar 6 (Folder 1010)
  - Vescey, Franz von (Folder 1011)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1887 (Folder 1012)
    Includes manuscripts of musical excerpts from Otello and correspondence to Victor Maurel.
  - Verdi, Giuseppe (Box 8, Folder 1140)
  - Verdi-Strepponi, Guiseppina (Folder 1013)
  - Verhunk, Fanchette, 1907 (Folder 1014)
  - Verron, Carl, 1908–1913 (Folder 1015)
  - Vial'tseva, Anastasia D., 1901–1904 (Folder 1016)
  - Vianna da Motta, Jose (Folder 1017)
  - Viardot, Pauline (Folder 1018)
  - Vieuxtemps, Henri (Folder 1019)
  - Vigano, Salvatore (Folder 1020)
  - Viglione, Borghese, 1912 Jan 10 (Folder 1021)
  - Vignas, Arturo, 1902 (Folder 1022)
  - Vignas, Francesco (Folder 1023)
  - Vinay, Ramon, 1953 (Folder 1024)
  - Vogelstrom, Fritz (Folder 1025)
  - Vogl, Josef, 1921 Apr 21 (Folder 1026)
  - Volpe, Arnold (Folder 1027)
  - Voss, Charles (Folder 1028)
  - Votto, Antonio (Folder 1029)
  - Walder, Mayo, 1919 (Folder 1030)
  - Wagner, Richard (Folder 1031)
  - Wagner, Siegfried, 1894 (Folder 1032)
  - Wagner, Siegfried (Box 8, Folder 1141)
  - Waldman, Maria (Folder 1033)
  - Walker, Edyth, 1898 (Folder 1034)
  - Waller, Lewis (Box 8, Folder 1142)
  - Walter, Gustav (Folder 1035)
  - Walter, Raoul (Folder 1036)
  - Warren, Leonard (Folder 1037)
  - Weber, Carl Maria von (Folder 1038)
  - Wedekind, Erika, 1908 (Folder 1039)
  - Weede, Robert, 1942 (Folder 1040)
  - Weidemann, Friedrich, 1910–1915 (Folder 1041)
  - Weidt, Lucy, 1908–1915 (Folder 1042)
  - Weltlinger, Sigmund (Folder 1043)
  - Werner-Mueller, Otto (Folder 1044)
  - Werrenrath, Reinald, 1929 Jan 12 (Folder 1045)
  - Westmoreland, Graf (Folder 1046)
  - Whitehill, Clarence, 1910-1916, 1929 (Folder 1047)
  - Wiborg, 1894 Jul 22 (Folder 1048)
  - Wieniawski, Henri, 1874 (Folder 1049)
  - Wieniawski, Joseph (Folder 1050)
  - Willmers, Rodolfo (Folder 1051)
  - Willmus (Folder 1052)
  - Winkelmann, Hermann, 1904 Apr 30 (Folder 1053)
  - Witherspoon, Herbert (Folder 1054)
  - Witherspoon, Herbert, 1910 (Box 8, Folder 1143)
  - Witten, Cora (Folder 1055)
  - Witten, Lawrence and Cora (Folder 1056)
  - Wittich, Alarie Maire (Folder 1057)
  - Wood, Sir Henry Joseph, 1910–1968 (Folder 1058)
  - Wulska, G. (Folder 1059)
  - Wyndhaus (Folder 1060)
  - Wyns, Charlotte (Folder 1061)
  - Zandonai, Riccardo (Folder 1062)
  - Zecchi, Carlo (Folder 1063)
  - Zeller, Heinrich (Folder 1064)
  - Zenatello, Giovanni, 1909 Jan 1 (Folder 1065)
  - Zenatello, Giovanni (Box 8, Folder 1144)
  - Ziegler, Karl (Folder 1066)
  - Zimbalist, Frem (Folder 1067)
  - Zottmeyer, Max (Folder 1068)
  - Zucchi, Virginia (Folder 1069)
  - Zucchini, Giovanni (Folder 1070)